<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About Me</string>
    <string name="name">Mihai Fecioru</string>
    <string name="yellow_star">Yellow Star</string>
    <string name="bio">

        Dear Madam/Sir
\n\n My name is Mihai-Daniel Fecioru, and I bring an experience of more than 20 years in technical leadership, people
management, project management and development of high-complexity software applications especially in domains
like distributed systems and bigdata applications (both batch and real-time) on top of public could infrastructure
(both AWS and Azure). During this time, I have acquired valuable expertise in the digital marketing domain, more
specifically in Data Management Platform (DMP) and Customer Data Platform (CDP) systems in my roles as head
of engineering for Adobe’s DMP (Adobe Audience Manager - http://www.adobe.com/solutions/mediaoptimization/audience-management.html) and then head of engineering for the User Profile Service which is a core
service in Adobe’s Real-Time CDP (Adobe Experience Platform -
https://experienceleague.adobe.com/docs/experience-platform/profile/home.html?lang=en).
\n\n I am highly motivated and passioned in constantly improving my skills in the area of building distributed systems
that offer best in class customer experience: reliability, performance and outstanding functional capabilities within
competitive costs. Throughout the years I have demonstrated these skills both in real-time systems (scaled the Adobe
DMP/CDP EDGE systems to support tens of billions of requests per day on multiple regions across the entire world
within 99.9 availability) and batch systems (scaled Adobe DMP/CDP systems to process more than 1 Petabytes of
data per day). I achieved these results by building and empowering a high-performing team (100 engineers across 3
continents) and by defining efficient processes to enable distributed software development, CI/CD best practices and
the on-call support needed to manage 24/7 services.
\n\n Besides the people management, project management and stakeholder / executive management skills, I am also
constantly investing in technical skills that allow me to better understand the realities / challenges of the systems I
own. My expertise is focused on designing / architecting / managing highly reliable distributed systems (both realtime and batch) on top of public cloud infrastructure (AWS and Azure) using technologies like: Java/Scala, Spark,
Akka, Spring, Kubernetes, Databricks, Aerospike, Cassandra, CosmosDB, Hadoop/HBase, kafka, Prometheus,
Grafana, Splunk etc.
\n\n I am living in Colorado Springs (Colorado, USA) and I am interested either a local/on-site role or a remote one (for
the last 5 years I have managed remote teams on 3 continents).
\n\n I consider that a position in your Company will give me the opportunity to use my qualifications and skills in
development and technical coordination of software projects and, at the same time, improve these skills through
exposure to new type of projects/challenges/environments.
\n\n For recommendations you can check my LinkedIn page: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mihai-fecioru-1008a4/
    </string>
    <string name="what_is_your_nickname">What is your nickname?</string>
    <string name="Done">DONE</string>
</resources>